xtensio.com 2019-12-09

# Privacy Policy - Agreement | Xtensio

_Last Updated: May 25th, 2018_

The Xtensio website (the “ **Site** ”) is operated by Xtensio, Inc. Xtensio is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. To that end, we have prepared this privacy policy (the “ **Privacy Policy** ”) to describe our information gathering, dissemination, and protection practices for the Site. The terms “ **Xtensio** ,” “ **we** ,” “ **us** ,” and “ **our** ” refer to Xtensio, Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliates. The terms “ **you** ,” “ **your** ,” and “ **yours** ” refer to the user/customer utilizing the Site. “ **Service** ” refers to Xtensio’s service which can be accessed via the Site. This Privacy Policy is governed by our [Terms of Use](https://xtensio.com/terms/).

###  **CONSENT**

By accessing our Service, you accept our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use, and you consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. In addition, by using our Service you are accepting the policies and practices described in this Privacy Policy. Each time you visit our Site, or use the Service, and any time you voluntarily provide us with information, you agree that you are consenting to our collection, use and disclosure of the information that you provide, and you are consenting to receive emails or otherwise be contacted, as described in this Privacy Policy. Whether or not you register or create any kind of account with us, this Privacy Policy applies to all users of the Site and the Service.

###  **COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**

We may collect both “Personally Identifiable Information” and “Non-Personally Identifiable Information” about you.

#### “ **Personally Identifiable Information** ”

This means any information which can be used to identify you. We may collect the following Personally Identifiable Information from you when you visit the Site, register an account, and/or use the Service: name, email address, location, IP address, phone number, billing address, and payment information. We endeavor to limit our requests for Personally Identifiable Information to information we believe is reasonably necessary to achieve our purposes as described in the “Information Use” section below. Any Personally Identifiable Information received in communication or in the material you transmit to the Site by electronic mail or otherwise are and will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

####  **“Non-Personally Identifiable Information”  **

This includes information that cannot be used to personally identify you, including, but not limited to:

  * Technical information about your computer or mobile device (such as type of device, web browser or operating system);
  * Your preferences and settings (time zone, language etc.);
  * The URL of the last web page you visited before coming to our Site;
  * The search terms you have looked up and results you selected; 
  * Communications between you and other users through our Site; and
  * How long you visited our Site and which services and features you used.

###  **INFORMATION USE**

Xtensio uses your Personally Identifiable Information for several general purposes. These include, but are not limited to:

  * Providing you with information and news about the Service;
  * Supporting the Service offered on the Site;
  * Contacting you for feedback about the Services;
  * Conducting research about Xtensio’s customer base or the Service;
  * Processing your payments including credit checks and collection;
  * Notifying you of technical updates or changes in policy; or
  * Contacting you for our own marketing and promotional purposes.

We may use non-Personally Identifiable Information such as demographic data to further improve the Site and the Service, and to track trends and analyze use patterns of the Service. This Privacy Policy does not limit in any way our use or disclosure of Non-Personal Information and we reserve the right to use and disclose such Non-Personal Information to our partners, advertisers and other third parties at our sole discretion.

###  **INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE**

We may disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to other companies or people for various reasons, including:

  * If sharing the information is reasonably necessary to provide the Service.
  * With vendors that provide a service, including, but not limited to, payment processing and collection (such as Stripe), email communication (such as Mailgun), and communication tools (such as HelpCrunch). 
  * With analytics companies (such as Google Analytics) which use tracking technologies to collect information about our users’ computer or mobile devices and their online activities in order to help us better understand how our Site is being used. 
  * To keep you up to date on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, or other information we think you would like to hear about either from us or from our business partners (unless you have opted out of these types of communications).
  * If we believe in good faith that we are required to do so by law, in connection with litigation, to prevent a crime, or to protect personal safety, the public, or the Site.
  * In connection with a sale or merger with another entity or if Xtensio should ever file for bankruptcy or have its assets sold to another entity.
  * When we otherwise have your consent to share the information.

Xtensio may also share non-Personally Identifiable Information with third parties (e.g. aggregate or demographic data).

###  **COOKIES**

When you visit our Site we may place “cookies” on your computer to recognize you.  We do this to enhance your experience on the Site (such as storing your preferences), collect statistical data, and track how you use our Site. For further information on how we use cookies and your rights related to them, please read our [Cookies Policy.](https://xtensio.com/cookies/)

###  **DO NOT TRACK**

Some browsers offer a “Do Not Track” feature, which notifies websites, web applications and services that you do not wish to have your online activities tracked. If you enable this setting in your browser, the functionality and experience of some features of the Site and the Service will be limited. For example, you may encounter problems saving the work you create on the Site.

###  **YOUR RIGHTS REGARDING THE USE OF YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**

At any time, you can correct, amend, delete or withdraw your consent for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your Personally Identifiable Information. You can do so in your account settings or by contacting us at this email address: [help@xtensio.com](mailto:help@xtensio.com). You may also ask us for a copy of the Personally Identifiable Information that we have collected from you. You have the right at any time to prevent us from contacting you for marketing purposes. When we send a newsletter or promotional communication to you, you can opt out of further communications by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in each e-mail.  Please note that notwithstanding the promotional preferences you indicate by either unsubscribing or opting out in the Settings section of the Site, we may continue to send you administrative emails including, for example, periodic updates to our Privacy Policy.

###  **DATA RETENTION**

We will retain your Personally Identifiable Information and non-Personally Identifiable Information for as long as you retain an active account on our Site. In the event that you close your account, your Personally Identifiable Information and non-Personally Identifiable Information will be deleted from our records. Likewise, if your account is inactive for more than one year, we will automatically close your account and delete all Personally Identifiable Information and non-Personally Identifiable Information associated with it.

###  **CHOICE**

We will request your consent before you provide us with your Personally Identifiable Information, which includes the opportunity to “opt in” to receiving direct marketing or market research information.

###  **SECURITY**

We implement reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices in order to protect your Personally Identifiable Information and ensure that such Personally Identifiable Information is not accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.  However, these measures do not guarantee that such information will not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of such precautions. By using our Service, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to assume these risks.

###  **THIRD PARTY SITES**

The Site may contain links to other sites. Xtensio is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when leaving the Site to read the privacy statements of each site that collects Personally Identifiable Information.

###  **THIRD PARTY RIGHTS**

This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of our Site.

###  **CHILDREN**

Our Site is not intended for use by children under the age of eighteen (18). We do not knowingly allow children under the age of eighteen (18) to register for any service, and we do not knowingly collect any Personally Identifiable Information from children under the age of eighteen (18).

###  **INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM USERS OUTSIDE OF THE UNITED STATES**

Our Site is intended only for residents of the United States. If you’re outside the United States and visit our Site, please be aware that your information will be sent to and stored in the United States, where our servers are located. By using our Site, you agree to the information collection, use, and sharing practices described in this Privacy Policy.

###  **YOUR CONSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

Xtensio reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post these changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Any such modifications become effective upon your continued access to and/or use of the Service five (5) days after we first post the changes on the website or otherwise provide you with notice of such modifications. It is your sole responsibility to check this website from time to time to view any such changes to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to any changes, if and when such changes may be made to this Privacy Policy, you must cease access to this website. If you have provided your email address to us, you give us permission to email you for the purpose of notification as described in this Privacy Policy.

###  **YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

If you are a resident of California, you have the right to request information from us once every calendar year regarding the manner in which we share certain categories of personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. You may request a copy of the information disclosed by sending an email to help@xtensio.com

###  **CONTACT**

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the practices of this Site, please contact us here:

Xtensio Inc.  
PO Box 93416  
Los Angeles, CA 90093

Email: help@xtensio.com
